{
    "subject": "Olav_V_of_Norway",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Princess_M\u00e4rtha_of_Sweden",
    "human_readable": "Olav V of Norway is married to Princess M\u00e4rtha of Sweden.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9401130676269531,
            "question": "To whom was Olav V of Norway married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9338095188140869,
            "question": "Who is Olav V of Norway married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9167856574058533,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Olav V of Norway and Princess M\u00e4rtha?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8153902292251587,
            "question": "Who is Olav V of Norway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7750346064567566,
            "question": "Is Princess M\u00e4rtha from Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6222200989723206,
            "question": "Who is Princess M\u00e4rtha?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6143569350242615,
            "question": "Is Olav V of Norway a king?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5542187690734863,
            "question": "Where is Princess M\u00e4rtha from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5089840888977051,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Princess M\u00e4rtha?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47202450037002563,
            "question": "What country did Olav V of Norway rule?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Olav V of Norway is married to Princess M\u00e4rtha of Sweden.",
            "html": "yago_21599_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Princess M\u00e4rtha?",
            "html": "yago_21599_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Princess M\u00e4rtha from?",
            "html": "yago_21599_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Olav V of Norway a king?",
            "html": "yago_21599_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21599_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21599_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21599_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21599_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21599_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21599_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21599_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21599_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21599_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21599_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. According to the context, Olav V was originally christened Alexander Edward Christian Frederick and was born on July 2, 1903. When his father was crowned king of Norway in 1905, the son became crown prince and was given the name Olav. In 1929 Crown Prince Olav married his cousin, Princess M\u00e4rtha of Sweden. This information confirms that Olav V is married to Princess M\u00e4rtha of Sweden."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that \"Olav V of Norway is married to Princess M\u00e4rtha of Sweden.\" Multiple documents, such as `3.txt`, `81.txt`, and `56.txt`, confirm this relationship."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}